cnova.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy & Cookies policy – CNOVA

**Privacy**

This policy applies to pages that are available via Cnova N.V’s website, the “Website” and includes all data, contents and computer code contained on or transmitted from the Website. This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you when you visit the Website, and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information. This policy does not apply to information collected offline or on any other websites, including through third party websites, applications or content that may be accessible on the Website or linked to by the Website. It also does not apply to information collected by Cnova N.V., any other users of the Website or any other third party (including affiliates, partners and other companies that we do not own or control and individuals that we do not employ or manage).

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, please do not use our Website. By accessing or using the Website, you agree to this privacy policy.

**Children Under the Age of 13**

Our Website and services are not intended for children under 13 years of age, and no one under age 13 may provide any personal information to us or through the Website or our services. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under age 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on our Website or on or through our services. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete it. If you believe we might have any personal information from or about a child under age 13, please [contact us](http://cnova.com/contact-us.html).

**Information that is Collected from you**

We will not collect any information about individuals, except where it is specifically and knowingly provided by them or as disclosed in this privacy policy.

When you visit our Website, our web server collects some basic information such as your internet service provider’s domain name, which pages you accessed on our Website, and when. We use this information to analyze the use of our Website to help guide improvements.

**Cookies**

When you visit our Website, we use cookies, which are small pieces of information that allow us to maintain your connection to our website. This Website may use cookies for detecting what kind of device you have in order to present content in the best way, for a language switch and/or for other purposes. These cookies do not collect or store any personally identifiable information. You can refuse the use of cookies on the Website as described below.

**Google Analytics**

This Website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses cookies (text files placed on your computer) to help the website operators analyze how users use the site. For more information about Google Analytics and its privacy practices, please see <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/>. By using this Website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out at the link provided above.

**How to Refuse the use of Cookies**

You may be able to refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings in your browser. However, if you do this you may lose some useful functionality such as personalization and “keep me signed in” and “remember me” features. Follow the links below to disable cookies on your browser:

**Disclosure of Your Information**

We will not share your information in identifiable form with any third party without your permission, except in the following circumstances: (i) as set forth in this Privacy Policy (for example, to our service providers); (ii) in response to a subpoena or when we are required to do so by law (for example, in response to a court order or other legal obligation); (iii) in response to a law enforcement agency’s request; (iv) to protect the security or confidentiality of our records or to enforce or apply our [NTD](http://cnova.com/site-services/terms-of-use.html); (v) in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary or appropriate to identify, contact, or take necessary action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with our or our users’ rights, or (vi) if we go through a reorganization (e.g., a merger into another organization or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding), in which case you will be notified via an announcement on the Website or otherwise, as we deem appropriate and subject to our being permitted to do so under contract or applicable law.

We may share your information with our affiliates and with certain trusted third parties to help us operate the Website and improve our business. For example, we may use third parties to host our data and the information of our users, provide customer service, distribute our newsletter, and for other services necessary to operate the Website or that may provide you a better experience on the Website.

**Third Parties**

The Website may contain content sponsored by third parties and links to third party websites, which are not controlled by us and which are not covered by this Privacy Policy. We do not control the use of automatic data collection technologies and handling of your information by third parties, and their use may be subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by this Privacy Policy. These third parties may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites or online services, and we do not currently take actions to respond to “do not track” signals. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based advertising or other targeted content. For more information about the policies of the third-party service providers and vendors that we work with, including your options for opting out of their use of tracking technologies, you should consult the policies at the links provided above. You are responsible for reviewing the privacy policies of these third-party service providers and vendors, as well as those of any third party website that you visit when you click on links made available on the Website. If you want to learn more about your options concerning interest-based advertisements, including your ability to opt-out, you can go to [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) or [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions about viewing or correcting information we have stored about you, or about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [contact@cnova.com](mailto:contact@cnova.com).

If you are a resident of the State of California in the United States, you have the right to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us using the information above.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Our Privacy Policy may change in the future. We encourage you to review this page periodically to understand our policy regarding our collection and use of your information. The Effective Date of this Privacy Policy, as stated below, indicates the last time this policy was revised. If we change this Privacy Policy, we will post the amended policy here with an updated Effective Date and notify you by posting an announcement on the Website, or by email or other means that we deem appropriate. Your continued use of the Website after notification of changes to this Privacy Policy constitutes your consent to the changes.
